paragonsports.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy - Paragon Sports

This Web site, currently located at www.paragonsports.com (“Web Site”), is published and maintained by Paragon Sports LLC et al, with offices located at 867 Broadway, New York, New York 10003 (“Paragon”). Paragon is referred to in this Privacy Policy as “we,” “us,” “our,” or other similar pronouns.

This Privacy Policy governs your use of the Web Site. This Privacy Policy explains, in general, what Personal Information (as defined below) and other information may be collected on our Web Site, how the information may be used, and with whom we may share such information. By visiting this Web Site, and/or using the services offered on or through this Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our services, this Privacy Policy may change, so check back to this page from time to time.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide to us, or that we may obtain, other than through our Web Site, such as by phone, through postal mail, in our retail stores and through other live and print media.

This Web Site is intended for users who are located in the United States of America. At this time, Paragon does not accept online orders shipped to International addresses. This Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States.

Advertisements and other content displayed or transmitted to you on or through the Web Site may be customized to your interests and preferences, based on your Personal Information and Web Site Usage Information, including (but not limited to) non-personally identifying information, which we may obtain from you or from other sources.

We collect Personal Information from and about users of our Web Site, for example, when users register or subscribe for accounts or features on our Web Site, make online purchases, complete surveys, contribute to a review, submit a comment or question to us using a “contact us” or similar feature on our Web Site, send us an e-mail, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via our Web Site.

We may also provide a feature that allows you to send information about our products to a friend by clicking on the “Send to Friend” or similar button on our Web Site or in an e-mail that we have sent you. In some of these cases (unless you simply forward our e-mail on your own), you may provide the name and e-mail address of your friend to us. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law. 

You may also be able to send an online card to a friend or family member, or send them a gift or gift certificate. If so, you may be required to provide us with your friend’s or family member’s Personal Information. Such information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law.

#### IP Address and Clickstream Data

When you visit our Web Site, our server automatically collects data about your Internet Protocol address, which is a number that’s automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider. When you request pages from our Web Site, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another Web site or a search engine); the pages you visit on this Web Site; the Web site you visit after this Web Site; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of Web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Web Site or a referral site; and other Web usage activity and data logged by our Web servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web Site. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider.

Any or all of these activities with regard to Web Site Usage Information may be performed on our behalf by our services providers.

### How is the Personal Information used?

We will use your Personal Information, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping.

In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, mailings, and the like), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the **Right to Opt In and Opt Out** section above.

We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Web Site and e-mails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

### Do we share Personal Information and Web Site Usage information with others?

#### Service Providers

We may use third-party partners to help operate our Web Site and deliver our products and services, and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Web Site or for our business (such as Web site or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).

#### Aggregate Statistics

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Web Site and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

#### Legally Compelled Disclosures

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including, but not limited to, in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of the Web Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

#### Business Transfer

In the event that Paragon, or substantially all of its assets, are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, reorganization, consolidation or liquidation, Personal Information may be one of the transferred assets.

By providing Personal Information to this Web Site, you understand and consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories.

### Third-Party “Linked-To” Web Sites

When you are on our Web Site you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other sites not operated by us. For example, if you choose to participate in a co-sponsored contest, sweepstakes or other offering that we may from time to time make available on the Web Site, you may be linked to the co-sponsor?s Web site. These sites may collect Personal Information about you. We do not control sites that are operated by these entities and we are not responsible for the information practices of these sites. This Privacy Policy does not address the information practices of those other Web sites. The Privacy Policies of these third party Web sites are located on those sites.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Web Site by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Web Site. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of our Web Site to sending you an e-mail.

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, you may contact us at customerservice@paragonsports.com or [1-800-961-3030](tel:+1-800-961-3030) or [212-255-8889](tel:+1-212-255-8889).

**Last Updated: [ 4/10/2008 ]**
